Now the eyes are completely done and they look fantastic.
But the finishing touch is now are the lips.
This is the signature point of this look is with the old Hollywood starlet it was normally that red, Madonna red, but with the flapper look, it was that more dark glossy, shiny... we are going to combine the two with a burgundy, shimmery, glossy type lip.
So, I am going to start with a burgundy lip liner.
She has nice full lips, so I am not going to overdraw her lips I am just going to trace her natural lip line and just fill it in with the lip liner.
This is where you create a nice shape for your lips, like that rosebud lips or if you like those pointed lips, which is up to you.
She has a great natural lip line so I am just going to trace that completely.
And again, fill it in because you don't want to see the lip liner.
You want it to all look natural and blended.
Also, filling in your lips with a lip liner will help your lipstick stay on longer and it will prevent from bleeding.
A lot of benefits from using a little bit of lip liner.
Keep it very neutral, you don't want it look like a harsh lip line, basically shaping the lips.
Now we are ready to start with the lipstick.